popunderzone.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy - PopunderZone

## Services Privacy

This privacy policy covers all of PopunderZone website and services. It does not, however, apply to other entities that PopunderZone does not own or control. By using or accessing PopunderZone.com, you agree to our privacy policy as provided herein.

PopunderZone is committed to protect your privacy. Due to this, any information collected, including your registration are submitted voluntarily at the visitor's will. PopunderZone will not share these information to a third party without your accord, or unless required by an governmental entity, or law.

## Cookies

Browsers are using cookies, and if you allow that, they will store small amount of data on your computer. PopunderZone will store some information about you so you will not be needed to go through login every time. PopunderZone will not use cookies to store personal data about you or your movement into our website. However please note if you reject cookies or disable them your surfing experience on our website may not be complete.

## Third Party cookie

We do not have access to cookie or information from a third party.

## Registration information

Our registration form require some personal data from you as: Your name, email, address. For payments we will require some specific payment data based on the chosen payment option. However these data collected will not be shared or sold.

## External Links

PopunderZone.com contain external links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policy from the website that you visit once left our website.
